Andrew Morrow

Full-stack web developer bringing a strong ability to breakdown complex code into comprehensible pieces for clients and my students alike. Many years of hands on end user troubleshooting experience gives me insight into how users are consuming current web based products.

Oxford, AL 36203 (678) 787-3449 asmorrow91@gmail.com Portfolio | Github LinkedIn

EXPERIENCE

Ironclad Technology Services — *Software Developer I* Remote

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

- Maintain and implement new features in government project https://cdp.dhs.gov/ using Javascript, jQuery, and React.
- * Refactor existing Bootstrap 4.X.X projects to Bootstrap 5.X.X
- ❖ Handle 508 compliance code updates and accessibility tool scans
- ❖ Work in Agile enviroment and achieve two week sprint deadlines

Trilogy Education Services — Senior Tutor, Teaching Assistant, Learning Assistant, Central Grader Remote

APRIL 2021 - PRESENT

- 200+ 1:1 sessions on MERN stack tutoring with colorful coding examples and breakdowns
- Leading the student with interactive pair programming coding challenges and examples
- Teaching students how to search documentation and be more self-sufficient

Proficiencies

React

NodeJS

Express

Javascript

iQuery

Redux

GraphQL

Bootstrap

TailwindCSS

SQL/MySQL

MongoDB

HTML/CSS

Git

EDUCATION

University of Central Florida — *Certification in Full-Stack Web Development*Orlando, FL

SEPTEMBER 2020 - MARCH 2021

Jacksonville State University — Computer Science Jacksonville, AL

AUGUST 2009 - AUGUST 2012